Someone sent that note to my wife, and I need to know who.
有人给我太太寄了这张纸条 我想知道是谁
Some secrets were discovered...
（有些秘密被发现了）
After my mom died, I started remembering what happened to Dana.
我妈妈死后 我开始回忆起发生在Dana身上的事
Who's Dana?
谁是Dana？
What are you doing here?
你在这干什么？
Some secrets were uncovered...
（有些秘密快要被揭穿了）
It could be any one of these guys she's having an affair with.
有可能是这些人中的某一个 和她有一腿
Don't worry about it. I'm not letting her out of my sight.
没关系，我会一直监视她
And some secrets...
（还有一些秘密……）
Jordana Geist manages to get her work done.
Jordana Geist能完成所有的工作
How do you cram it all in?
你的秘诀是什么？
Were shared.
（……被共享了）
That's A.D.D. medication.
这是ADD药物？
Competition --
（竞争的）
it means different things to different people.
（意义因人而异）
In suburbia, it means keeping up with the Joneses.
在Suburbia竞争意味着 赶上Joneses的步伐
On Wisteria Lane,
而在Wisteria Lane
that means keeping up with Bree Van De Kamp.
竞争意味着 可以和Bree Van De Kamp一较高下
Everyone knew Bree had the nicest lawn in the neighborhood,
每个人都知道在这个社区里 Bree的草坪是最美丽的
and no one be grudged her this.
没有人敢挑战这个地位
No one, that is,
没有人, 那是指
except Martha Huber,
除了Martha Huber
whose own lawn paled in comparison.
相比而言她的手艺要 逊色许多
No matter how carefully she trimmed...
不管她多么精心的打理
or how lovingly she watered...
多么仔细的浇水
or how generously she fertilized...
多么慷慨的施肥
the grass was always greener on the other side of the fence.
栅栏那边的草总比 这么要更绿
Hello, Victor. How are you today?
你好，Victor 今天怎么样？
Out jogging again?
又在慢跑？
I can't catch my breath.
我喘不上气了
Would you like a slurp from my hose?
需要我给你浇点水吗？
Victor?
Don't worry.
别担心
I'm going to get an ambulance.
我去叫救护车
Then one day Mrs. Huber finally got the chance to mow down the competition.
这一天Huber终于找到 扭转竞争形势的机会了
Help!
救命!
Somebody help!
有人帮忙吗!
What happened?
哦，发生什么事了?
He collapsed on your hydrangeas.
他在你们家的草坪上晕倒了
Call 911!
快打911！
Yes, Mrs. Huber understood the first rule of competition --
是的，Huber懂得竞争的要诀
in order to win, you have to want it more.
如果你想赢就得多加小心
Episode 7 : Anything You Can Do
第7集 : 你能做的一切事情
When I was alive,
我活着的时候
my friends and I came together once a month for a meeting of the Wisteria Lane book club.
我和我的朋友每月聚会一次 这是Stere Alan的读书俱乐部
We found the problems of literary characters so absorbing --
我们发现文学人物的问题如此吸引人
the way they dealt with adversity,
她们如何面对困境
conducted illicit affairs,
如何处理非法恋情
endured domestic dramas,
忍受家庭内部矛盾
and planned romantic conquests.
策划浪漫的追求方式
But since my death, my friends had lost their interest in fiction.
我死后我的朋友们 对小说失去了兴趣
So... what did everybody think?
你们觉得怎么样？
Their own problems had become absorbing enough.
她们自己的问题已经 够麻烦的了
I thought the character of Madame Bovary was very inspirational.
我觉得Madame Bovary 这个人物形象很鼓舞人心
Inspirational?
鼓舞人心?
She poisons herself with arsenic.
她服砒霜自尽
Really?
真的?
You didn't read until the end?
你没有读完？
I stopped after page 50.
我读到50页
Am I the only one who read the book?
我是唯一读完这本书的人？
I saw the movie. It was really good.
我看了电影 非常棒
Ladies, I'm sorry, but
女士们, 对不起, 但是……
what is the point of having a book club if we don't read the book?
如果我们都不读书 那要一个读书俱乐部干什么？
More wine?
再来点酒?
So, uh, Reba, Emma, and Laurie,
那么, 哦, Reba, Emma, and Laurie,
would you girls come to the kitchen and help me with the snacks?
你们能到厨房帮我点忙吗？
Sure.
当然可以
I will be right in.
我马上就过来
God,  I couldn't wait to get rid of them.
上帝, 我迫不及待得要打发走她们
Okay,
听着
so Lynette said that you found Zach.
Lynette 说你找到Zach了
He's at a rehabilitation center,
他在一个康复中心
and Julie snuck in and actually talked to him.
Julie溜进去和他说上话了
Did he say anything about his mother's suicide?
他说了关于他妈妈自杀的事了吗?
There wasn't enough time, but he did say one thing that was kind of mysterious.
时间很紧，他没有说什么神秘的事情
He said something happened to someone named Dana,
他说事情和一个叫Dana的人有关
and that he could never, ever talk about it.
然后就没机会说了
Who the hell's Dana?
该死的Dana是谁？
That's  the mystery part.
这是最神秘的部分
I figure Dana has something to do with what Mary Alice was trying to hide.
我觉得Dana和Mary Alice 竭力隐藏的某些东西有关
So somebody found out Mary Alice's secret...
有人发现了Mary Alice的秘密……
and sent the note.
然后寄给她这张纸条
So who the hell is that?
那个人到底是谁？
The stationery is parchment number 17, 100% cotton.
信纸是17号仿羊皮纸，100%棉的
It's made by Cypress Office Products.
它是由Cypress Office公司生产的
They have stores in 12 cities, including yours.
他们在12个城市有专卖店 包括你居住的城市
Now, I traced that postmark back to your local post office.
我拿着邮戳去问了当地的邮局
Meaning?
然后呢?
Meaning that the blackmailer is probably someone you know --
然后发现威胁者很可能是你认识的
a neighbor, milkman...
邻居、送牛奶的、……
pool boy, soccer mom.
水管工、球僮
Soccer mom?
球僮?
Mr. Young, sometimes evil drives a minivan.
Young先生, 有时候邪恶会开着小卡车驾到
I had this gig once
我有过这样的经历
tracking down this PTA mom who was hell-bent on landing her daughter
我曾经追捕一个孩子的母亲 她拼命的把女儿往地上扔
a spot on the parade float.
在游行的花车上
Fed antifreeze to half the homecoming committee.
联邦调查局封锁了 一半来到学校的的监护人
Did  you catch her?
你抓到她了吗？
Mr. Young...
Young先生...
the people who hired me didn't hire me to catch her.
我的雇主并没有雇我去抓住她
Wow, honey, --
哇呜，亲爱的，……
this place looks spotless.
这儿看起来完美无瑕
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey, so, listen,
嗨，听着
Great. You want to run it by me?
好极了，需要我帮你吗？
No, I'm good.
不用，我可以的
But  thanks.
谢谢你
Okay.
好吧
Well, that's the thing. You know how whenever I pitch in the boardroom at work,
不过，问题是只要我在会上提出我的建议
and Hennessy always tears my ideas down in front of the partners?
Hennessy总是在同事跟前反驳我
Yeah.
嗯
I invited the partners and their wives over so I could pitchto them here,
我邀请了我的同事和他们的妻子 这样我就能在家和他们沟通我的想法
and I thought maybe we could make a formal dinner for six, we could sit, we could --
我想也许我们在六点钟能有个正式的晚宴 这样我们能坐在一起，可以……
and when exactly would this formal dinner take place?
这个正式晚宴要在什么时候举办？
Uh, day after tomorrow.
呃，后天
- Tom. - Yeah, I know, I know,
- 哦,我知道，我知道
I know it's short notice. I just --
我知道这太突然 我只是……
You think?  How am I supposed to pull off a formal dinner with no warning?
你认为？我怎么可以在毫无准备的情况下 举办一个正式的晚宴？
I don't know. Bree Van De Kamp does this kind of thing all the time.
我不知道 Bree Van De Kamp 总是能做到这一点
What did you say?
你刚说什么？
Wow, I'm sorry. I didn't mean it like that.
哇呜，对不起，我不是那个意思
That's -- you know what? Forget it. I'll call, and I'll cancel.
我是说，这样的，算了 我打电话取消掉
Just don't worry about it.
别为这事担心了
No, no, let's --let's do it.
不，不，我们可以举办的
Really?
真的？
Yeah. It's good for your career. I'll pull it off.
是的，这对你的事业有好处 我还筹备
Yes. Honey, thank you so much.
哦，亲爱的，太谢谢你了
You know what? I promise, I land this account,
知道吗，我欠你个人情，我保证
and I'm going to buy you something awful pretty.
我会给你买一些极其漂亮的东西
Luckily for Tom, Lynette had a recipe for success.
对Tom来说，幸运的是 Lynette 有一个成功的秘诀
Unfortunately for her,
不幸的是
she was missing the secret ingredient.
她忘记了秘诀的配方
- Yeah.
- 你好
It's me.
是我
Don't turn around. My mother-in-law can see you.
别回头 我婆婆能看见你
I hate that she's always watching us.
我讨厌她总是监视我们
So meet me at the motel in an hour?
一小时内我们在汽车旅馆见？
John?
Uh, I've got plans.
呃，我有安排了
So cancel.
你要取消？
They're with Danielle. We're going to the movies.
我要和Danielle去看电影
That sounds like a date.
听起来像是去约会
Yeah.
是的
Well, I have a problem with you seeing other girls.
看见你和别的女孩在一起我很不习惯
Well, I have a problem with you having a husband.
我看见你有一个丈夫也很不习惯
I guess we'll both have to learn to deal.
我想我们都得学会去适应
Don't even try to make it up to me by talking dirty.
想都别想用一些下流的话来补偿我
Hello?
喂？
Mr. and Mrs. Van De Kamp.
Van De Kamp先生和Van De Kamp夫人
So your son decided to entertain some of his friends yesterday
昨天你的儿子想取悦他的朋友
by shoving a freshman's head into a locker.
把一个大一新生的头撞到柜子上
This was the Johnson boy?
是Johnson家的孩子吗？
Yes. He broke the boy's nose.
是的，你儿子打坏了他的鼻子
Because of our no-tolerance policy, your son may face expulsion.
本着严惩的原则 你儿子将要被开除
You're going to ruin his whole future over a little rough housing?
你们要因为他的这个小小的破坏行为 而去毁掉他的前程？
Rex, this was practially assault.
Rex, 这叫攻击
Mrs. Stark, what Andrew did was clearly wrong,
Stark夫人，很明显Andrew所作所为是非常不好的
but in his defense, his mother and I are going through severe marital problems.
但我要为他说两句 她的妈妈和我正在面临严重的婚姻问题
How is that relevant?
这两个有什么关系？
Our marriage is disintegrating.
我们的婚姻正走向破裂
Of course Andrew is acting out. He has every right to be angry.
所以Andrew的行为有些反常 他有理由生气
If Andrew's angry about you moving out of the house,
如果Andrew是因为你搬出家而气愤
then perhaps he should shove your head into a locker.
那也许他应该把你的头撞到柜子上
All I'm saying is that we need to take some of the responsibility here.
我只是想我这件事我们也需要承担责任
So does Andrew.
Andrew也有责任
Blaming his actions on our problems --
把他的行为归咎于我们的问题
which are not so serious --
况且我们的问题并不严重
does not help him.
并不能帮助他
Our problems are serious.
我们的问题很严重
Mrs. Stark, you handle this however you see fit.
Stark夫人,你们觉得合适的时候 再来讨论这个问题吧
Bree, I've gone to an attorney.
Bree, 我找了律师
You're going to be served with divorce papers later today.
今天晚些时候你就会接到离婚文件
You went to an attorney?
你找了律师？
Yeah.
是的
And a good one, too.
而且是个非常棒的律师
Well, he better be good,
他最好能强点
because when I'm finished with you,
因为如果咱俩完了的话
you won't have a cent to your name.
你别想在你名下有一分钱
Bring it on.
都拿走吧
Perhaps detention is the way to go.
也许我们可以拘留他
Mom, you're getting too dressed up.
妈妈，你打扮得有些过火了
I know, but I want to look really sexy.
我知道，我想看起来性感一点
I told Mike I expect him to have you home by 11:00.
我告诉Mike 我希望他十一点之前送你回家
Hmm. How about midnight?
嗯，十二点怎么样？
All right, but no later. You know how I worry.
好吧，不能再晚了 你知道我担心什么
So, you, uh, got protection?
你，有保护措施吗？
Oh, my god.
哦，上帝
We are so not having this conversation.
我们不能谈这些
We are, because I enjoy being an only child.
可以，因为我喜欢做你的独生子
Are you finished?
你说完了吗？
Almost.
快了
You know, I always assumed I'd have sex for the first time before you had it again.
我总是在想 我也许会在你的第二次性爱之前，献出我的初夜
Okay, you can leave now, mm-hmm.
好了，你现在可以走了
Yeah.
耶
What do you think? Trying too hard?
你觉得怎么样？太正式？
Yeah, well, what do you know?
是的，你想说什么？
It's  80 degrees outside, and you're wearing fur.
外面有80度，你却穿着毛料
Hey, Mike.
你好，Mike
Hey, Edie.
你好, Edie
Wow. Get a load of you.
哇呜，你的盛装艳裹
Ooh, you look so pretty.
看起来很漂亮
I hardly recognize you.
我差点没认出来你
Oh, this?
哦，这件？
Well, I have a date right now with Mike.
我和Mike有个约会，现在
We kissed.
我们有过接吻了
FYI.
仅供参考.
Ooh, love that jacket. Good choice.
哦，我喜欢这件外套 很好的选择
Um, look, Susan, I'm really sorry, but I've got to cancel.
Susan，真的很抱歉 我必须取消约会
I have an...
我有个
unexpected houseguest.
不速之客
Coming through.
接通了
Oh, sorry. Hi, I'm Kendra.
哦，打扰了 你好，我是Kendra
Susan.
我是Susan
I'm going to run to the car and get my stuff.
我要去车上拿我的行李
I  know how this looks, but there's nothing between us.
我知道这看起来容易让人误会 但我们之间没什么
Kendra's just an old friend.
Kendra只是一个老朋友
Old friend.
老朋友
Yeah, you know --
是的，你知道
Yeah, yeah.
是的，我知道
No, actually, no, I don't know.
不，事实上，我不知道
So by "old friend," you mean college pal, bowling buddy, saved you from drowning?
老朋友，你是说大学同学，保龄球玩伴 在你溺水时救你的人？
It's hard to explain.
这很难解释
Could you give it a shot?
你能说清楚一点吗？
Mike, I'm going to go upstairs and take a shower.
Mike，我要上楼去洗个澡
Look, I promise I'll make this up to you.
我保证以后会向你解释
And...
还有
you look amazing.
你看起来美得惊人
Mike, where are the towels?
Mike，毛巾在哪？
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey!
嗨！
How was your big date?
你的约会怎么样？
Mike had to reschedule.
Mike要另外安排时间
Oh, because of the hot girl with the suitcase over there?
是因为那个提着箱子的惹火女郎？
Gosh, how devastating for you.
哦，那对你打击太大了
FYI.
仅供参考
Look, I just want to move this place fast. I'll do whatever we have to do.
我想尽快搬出这个地方 我会尽力而为
Well, that's good to know.
哦，那就好了
You do realize that you're going to have to disclose the fact that your wife killed herself in the house.
你确实意识到你必须公开 你妻子在这间屋子自杀的事实？
I am?
是吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的
Legal crap.
法律的烂规定
You know, people get really freaked out by suicides.
人们对自杀还是很害怕的
I can't blame them. Hell.
不能怪他们
I get the willies just standing here.
我站在这就觉得毛骨悚然
Is there any way to get around it?
有办法不公开吗？
Off the record?
修改记录？
Yeah.
是的
You could say that she shot herself in the living room
你可以说她在客厅开枪
and then crawled out back to die.
然后爬出去才死的
Well, I'm just saying.
我只是这么说说而已
Oh, I got to go. I'll call you tomorrow.
哦，我得走了，我明天给你打电话
Edie, wait.
Edie, 等等
Paul had always known Edie Britt was capable of doing anything to close a deal.
Paul 知道为了达成交易 Edie可以不择手段
But now he realized she was capable of so much more.
但是现在他意识到 她能做的还不止这些
Hey, Danielle.
嗨, Danielle
Hey, Mrs. Solis.
嗨， Mrs. Solis
Oh, Danielle...
哦, Danielle...
remember when you said you wanted to be a model?
记得你说过你想当一个模特？
You remember that? That was, like, last summer.
你还记得？好像是去年夏天我说的
Well, as it turns out, Percik Modeling Academy has an opening for their summer program.
是的，Percik 模特学校夏季的培训开始了
Would you like me to sponsor you?
你愿意让我资助你吗？
Would I?  Oh, my god. That's, like, one of the best schools in the country.
我吗？哦，天啊， 这是最好的模特学校之一
You would do that for me?
你愿意资助我？
I sure would.
当然愿意
I would so love to go to New York.
我非常想去纽约
Oh, and I would so love to help you get there.
哦，我也非常想帮助你去那儿
Hey, Jordana.
嗨, Jordana.
Hey, Lynette. How are you?
嗨, Lynette. 你还好吗?
You look a little tired. Is everything okay?
你看起来很疲惫，一切都好吗？
Actually, I'm getting ready for a dinner party tomorrow night -- six people.
事实上，我正在准备明天晚上的晚宴－－六个人
Sounds fun.
听起来很有趣
Big fun.
太有趣了
Say, you wouldn't have any of your kids' A.D.D. medication that you could spare just to get me over the hump --
你有没有孩子们吃的的ADD药物 可以帮我度过难关？
Tina!
Don't push your sister.
别推你姐姐
Gosh, Lynette,
该死, Lynette
I'm really running low.
我状态不好
I need all my energy I can get.
我需要补充能量
My sister Elaine and her kids are flying in town for a week.
我姐姐Elaine和她的孩子们 这周飞来看我
Yeah, that's exciting. I wish my sister would visit more often.
哦，那太好了 我希望我姐姐能经常来看我
Yeah, sisters are great.
是啊，有姐姐真好
Yeah.
是的
Just three or four pills. I'm really hitting a wall here.
只要三四片就行了 我真的走投无路了
Yeah, the come-down can be a real bitch.
是的，精力不够真是很麻烦
I wish I could help.
真希望我能帮你
I'm not going to forget about this, Jordana.
我不会忘记这件事的，Jordana
What's that supposed to mean?
你什么意思？
It means come girl scout cookie time,
意思是孩子们聚会的时候
don't bother bringing around little Tina, because we won't be home.
别把Tina 带来，因为我们不在家
What's all this about?
什么事？
You both know that your mother and I have been unhappy for quite a while.
你们都知道我和你们的妈妈 有些不愉快
After a lot of soul-searching, we've decided that it would be better if we got divorced.
深思熟虑之后，我们决定离婚会更好一些
But whatever problems your father and I may have,
但是不管我和你爸爸有什么问题
it doesn't change the fact that we love you very, very much.
不会改变我们爱你们的事实
I've got a question.
我有个问题
Go  ahead, sweet heart. Ask whatever you want.
问吧，宝贝，你可以随便问
Can I live with dad?
我能和爸爸住在一起吗
I mean, come on, mom, let's face it -- we drive each other crazy.
我是说，妈妈，面对现实吧 我们快把对方逼疯了
Is -- is that what you would prefer, Danielle -- to live with your father?
Danielle ，你是不是也更愿意和你爸爸住在一起？
I don't really care as long as I have my own bathroom.
我不介意和谁住，只要我有自己的浴室
Um... all this, um,
呃，所有这一切，呃
wine is, uh, giving me a headache.
这酒让我头很疼
Six weeks in the suburban jungle and this is all you got?
你在郊区呆了六个星期 就查到了这些？
There are over 300 families in this subdivision.
这个地方有三百多户人家
It'll take time to check them all out.
把他们都查清楚需要时间
Dad said last time he saw you, you were ready to quit.
爸爸说上次他看到你时 你想辞职不干了
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
是的，我改变主意了
This is a gigantic waste of your time, and my father's money.
这对你的时间和我爸爸的金钱 都是一种巨大的浪费
What, are you afraid of the old man burning through your inheritance?
你是怕那个老头把你的遗产提前花光了？
That's not funny.
这个玩笑并不可笑
Mike, here's the thing.
Mike, 问题就在这儿
What?
什么?
Dad can't chase ghosts alone.
我爸爸不可能一个人去查那个幽灵
If you stop, he'll have to accept it's over.
如果你不干了 他不得不承认，事情结束了
Let me have my father back.
让我把我爸爸拉回来
If I quit, he'll just hire somebody else.
如果我辞职 他会再雇别人的
Not if you tell him there's nothing here to find.
如果你告诉他这儿没什么可查的 他就不会
Well, I can't do that.
我不能那么做
What happens when your girlfriend finds out you're not just this sweet, neighborly plumber?
如果你的女朋友发现 你并不是那个甜蜜的水暖工邻居会怎么样？
You're lying to her, Mike.
你在对她撒谎, Mike
Oh, here it is.
哦，给你这个
Great.
好的
This will keep the crab dip warm.
这个能保持蟹肉的温度
It took forever to shell the little buggers, but it'll be worth it.
给这些小东西去壳太费劲 但很值得
You shelled your own crabs?
你自己去壳？
Okay, I don't want to butt in, but are you doing too much?
我不想多嘴 但你是不是干得太多了？
'Cause you look exhausted.
因为你看起来疲惫极了
Oh, I'm fine. I just need some coffee.
我没事，喝点咖啡就好了
Thank you.
谢谢你
Oh, my god. Look at this embroidery.
哦，天啊 看看这个刺绣
Where did this come from?
这从哪里来的？
Paul Young's garage sale.
Paul Young的甩卖
Dana.
Wow.
哇呜
Dana was a baby.
Dana 是个婴儿
Surprise.
给你个惊喜
No way.
不可能
Yep.
是的
No way.
不可能
Nah, it's all yours. Here are the keys.
是你的了，这是钥匙
Rex, what's this about?
Rex, 这是什么回事?
I went and splurged a little.
我花钱买的
Oh, Danielle, here's your present.
哦, Danielle, 这是你的礼物
Luggage?
行李？
Yeah. It's to take with you to the Percik Mmodeling Aacademy.
是的，它会和你一起去Percik模特学校
I'm footing the entire bill.
我付全部的费用
You mean it?  I can really go to new york?
你说真的？我真的能去纽约？
Wait. Wait a minute. What's all this about a modeling academy?
等等，等一下 什么模特学校
It's my new career. Mrs. Solis is sponsoring me.
我的新职业 Solis夫人资助的
Oh, is she now? And when were you planning on telling me?
哦，现在吗？ 你们打算什么时候告诉我？
She told me, and I think it's a great idea.
她刚跟我说的，我觉得是个好主意
Don't you two see what he's doing?
你们俩知道他在干什么吗？
He's trying to get you on his side. He's trying to buy your love.
他想让你们站在他那边 他想收买你们的爱
Oh, for god's sake, don't be paranoid.
哦，看在上帝的份上，别这么偏激
A car? A modeling academy?
汽车？模特学校？
You should have discussed these gifts with me first.
你应该先和我商量一下这些礼物的事
I'm sorry, kids, but we cannot accept them.
孩子们，对不起， 但是我们不能接受这些
Dad, you can't let her do this.
爸爸，你不能让她这么做
Bree, we just told the kids we're getting divorced. Isn't it time to spoil them a little?
Bree，我们刚刚告诉孩子们我们要离婚 难道不该对他们好点吗？
I said no.
我说了不行
You know what?
知道吗？
They're my kids, too, and I can give the many thing I want.
他们也是我的孩子 我想给什么就给什么
There you go.
你们走吧
- Thank you, daddy.
- 谢谢你，爸爸
Yes!
好极了!
Did you offer to help Danielle get into modeling school?
你主动提出资助Danielle 去上模特学校？
What?
什么？
Uh, yes.
呃，是的
No. Um...
不是，嗯
is that how she heard it?
那她怎么知道？
Yes. Gabrielle, did you or did you not offer to sponsor her?
Gabrielle,你到底有没有资助她？
I just wanted to help out.
我只是想帮个忙
It's in New York, for god's sakes. Why on earth would you suggest that?
那在纽约，你到底为什么要这么做
It's her dream, and don't you want her to be happy?
这是她的梦想 你难道不想让她快乐？
No.
不
And in the future, I would appreciate you keeping your ridiculous ideas to yourself.
谈到梦想，我希望你把 你那个荒谬的主意留给你自己吧
Bree.
Bree
John.
John
John!
You're so jealous of Danielle, you try to ship her off to New York?
你嫉妒Danielle 所以想把她弄到纽约？
I'm not jealous. I just don't like to share.
我不是嫉妒 只是不喜欢和别人分享
Well, you know what? I quit. The yard, us, everything.
知道吗？我不干了 那个花园，还有一切
Oh, don't be that way.
哦，别那样做
Well, what's the point if we can never be together?
如果我们不能在一起 那还有什么意义？
You know, an hour here, an hour there.
一会在这儿，一会在那儿
I don't want us to end on a bad note.
我不想我们这样不愉快的结束
Carlos has this black-tie thing tonight.
Carlos今晚要出席一个正式场合
- I could slip out
- 我可以溜出来
-
Mrs. Solis
Solis夫人
-
John, please.
John, 求你了
What we had was so special.
我们曾经有过的是那么特别
I think it deserves a proper goodbye.
值得有个很好的分手
We'd, um...
我们，呃
we'd still be over, though.
不过，我们还是结束了
Of course.
当然
I knew this play date was a good idea.
我知道这个聚会是个好主意
Yeah, thank you for suggesting it.
是的，谢谢你的建议
Your boys are the only ones I know who could tire out Timmy.
你的孩子们是唯一能 让Timmy玩得尽兴的
Yep, he's a feisty one.
是的，他太多动了
Hey, word on the street is, um, you've been medicating Timmy?
嗨，说真的，你一直给Timmy吃药？
Oh, yeah, for his A.D.D.
哦，是的，因为他的ADD
The pills have been a god send.
那些药丸这是天赐良药
I bet.
我敢打赌说是
Can I use your bathroom?
我能用你的洗手间吗？
As Lynette swallowed the stolen medication of an 8-year-old child,
当 Lynette吞下她偷来的 给八岁孩子吃的药丸时
she vowed she'd never again sink to such depths...
她曾发誓过再也不吃的
anytime soon.
很快
Well, it looks like you've got your black mailer.
看起来你找到了那个要挟遮
Is it time to bring in the police?
是时候报警了吗？
That's not really an option for me.
我不想这么做
Mm.
姆
Before my wife shot herself,
在我妻子自杀之前
we lived a life that I was proud of.
我们过着另我满足的生活
We loved each other,
我们相亲相爱
we had values, we went to church,
我们价值观一样 我们去教堂
we gave to charity.
我们去捐赠
We were good people, Mr. Shaw.
我们是好人，Shaw先生
Oh, I believe you.
哦，我相信你
That's why it's so incomprehensible to me that Edie Britt would try to destroy us.
这就是为什么我不能理解 Edie为什么要破坏我们
Well, you've suffered a great loss.
你蒙受了巨大的伤痛
For your pain to heal, that's going to take some time.
要想治愈还需要一段时间
I can't wait.
我等不及了
I need help now.
我现在需要帮助
For 5 grand, she's hurt.
5000美元，她会受伤
10 grand, she's gone.
10000美元，她会没命的
Mom, what's going on?
妈妈，怎么了？
Oh, I'm throwing you out.
我把你们的东西扔出去了
I've separated all your things into two sides.
我把你们的东西分成两部分
This side is yours, Danielle, and the other one is Andrew's.
这是你的, Danielle 另一边是Andrew的
Okay, you-- you've lost it.
好的，你，你疯了吧
Where are we supposed to live?
那我们要住哪？
Darned if I know.
我怎么会知道
Uh, Danielle, everything in the north quadrant of your side is clothes and books and such,
呃, Danielle, 北边那个角 是你的衣服，书，和……
and the south side are miscellaneous items.
南边是其它的东西
Mom, this isn't going to work, okay? I'm not giving up my car.
妈妈，你这么做没用，知道吗？ 我不会放弃我的车的
That's a smart idea, because you're probably going to have to sleep in it for a while.
你说得对，因为你可能得在里面住上一段日子
Mom, you can't stop us from going back inside the house.
妈妈，你不可能不让我们进屋的
Oh, no? That's Mr. Conlan, the locksmith. He's been very helpful today.
不可能？那是Conlan先生，锁匠 他今天帮了我大忙
Of course, I could give you the new keys,
当然，我会给你们新钥匙
which would mean you'd have to adhere to my rules,
前提是你们得听我的
which include giving back your father's gifts.
包括放弃爸爸给你们的礼物
Okay, fine, you win. I won't go to New York.
好吧，你赢了 我不去纽约了
I'm outta here.
我搬出去
Oh, hello.
你好
- Welcome. I'm Edie.
- 欢迎你，我是 Edie.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
你好，很高兴认识你
An open house in the suburbs?
郊区的开放参观日？
This is beyond kitsch.
这太俗了
Just be have yourself.
你收敛一点
This is one of the houses on the street I've had a hard time getting into.
街上的这间房子 我一直没有机会进去
God, I wish you would let this go.
上帝，真希望没有这码事
I'm taking you out for drinks tonight.
今天晚上我带你出去喝酒
There's this cowboy bar called the Saddle Ranch you need to see.
有一个叫Saddle Ranch 的 牛仔酒吧，你需要去看看
Why?
为什么？
It's the last place anybody ever saw your sister.
这是别人最后看见你姐姐的地方
Susan.
What brings you here?
你怎么来这了？
I just wanted to say goodbye to Mary Alice's house
我只是想对Mary Alice的房子说再见
before somebody else moved in.
在有别人搬进来之前
Aw.
哦
That sounds almost plausible.
听起来似乎很有道理
I beg your pardon?
你说什么？
Oh, come on.
别这样
We both know why you're here,
我们都知道你为什么在这儿
and the answer is yes, they are having sex.
你猜对了 他们有不正当关系
No question.
绝对没错
You don't know what you're talking about. They're just friends.
你根本不知道你在说什么 他们只是朋友
Hmm. Think so?
姆，你这么认为？
I overheard them say that they're going to the Saddle Ranch tonight
我偷听到他们说 今晚要去Saddle Ranch
for drinks and dancing.
喝酒，跳舞
So? Friends can do that.
那又怎么样 朋友也可以的
Oh, my god. I just want to slap and shake you.
哦，上帝 我真想打你一巴掌让你清醒
Where did you say they were going tonight?
你刚说他们今晚要去哪？
I don't know why I let you talk me into coming here.
我不知道为什么我会听你的 来到这
There is obviously nothing going on between them.
很明显他们之前什么也没有
Where are you going?
你要去哪？
I'm going to the bathroom, and then I'm going home.
洗手间，然后回家
I don't want Mike to catch me here.
我不想让Ｍｉｋｅ在这看到我
It's only been 10 minutes.
才过了十分钟
She could be waiting to make her move.
她可能在等待时机
Oh, come on. You're not going to beat a girl like that by knocking off early.
哦，别这样 这样草草收场你是不可能打败她的
It's not a competition.
这不是竞争
The hell it isn't.
鬼才相信呢
Good night, Edie.
晚上好，Edie
Suit yourself.
随便你
But for the record...
但是我郑重声明
I was rooting for you to land him.
我希望你能赢得他
And why would you root for me?
你为什么站在我这边？
Well, I figured it'd be easier for me to steal Mike from you than her.
我觉得从你手里抢走 Mike 比从她手里容易
She seems like fun.
她看起来很可笑
Just take some ant acid.
吃点蚁酸吧
It's not those kind of cramps.
不是那种痛法
This is a business dinner.
只是商务宴会
It's important.
很重要
Mm.
嗯
Relax.
行了
You and I can go alone.
咱们倆去就行了
Gabrielle can stay here and get better.
Gabrielle 呆在这儿可以好一点
Fine.
好吧
See you in a couple of hours.
几小时后见
Okay.
好的
Take good care of Carlos.
照顾好Carlos
Oh, I always do.
哦，我一直在照顾他
Go, Edie!
加油, Edie!
Oh, god.
Oh, 天哪
Mike.
Mike
What a small, small world.
世界真小
Yeah, it sure is.
是的，没错
I caught Edie hiding in the back.
我看见Edie藏在后面
No kidding. Is she here?
开玩笑吧 她也在这？
Yeah.
是的
Yeah, she said, um, "the jig is up," and then she went to ride the bull.
是的，她说，“吉格舞开始了” 然后她就去骑公牛了
Oh, and she said you two came together.
哦，她说你们俩一起来的
Oh, well, yeah. W-we did.
哦，是的
Uh, I just thought she left.
呃，我刚刚还以为她走了
Are you following me?
你在跟踪我？
What?
什么？
No.
没有
No, I just came here, you know, with Edie.
我只是来这儿 和Edie一起
We just love to ride that bull.
我们只是喜欢骑那头公牛
You ride the bull?
你骑公牛
Yeah. Yeah, it's a real rush.
是，是的，太刺激了
Come on, Susan. Give me a break.
算了，Susan. 让我休息一下
No, you know, you give me a break.
不，你让我休息一下吧
I did not follow you here, and even if I had followed you here,
我没有跟踪你 即使我跟踪了
it's just because you've been so secretive about Kendra.
那也是因为你对Kendra太遮遮掩掩了
Kendra and I are friends.
Kendra 和我只是朋友
And I came here to ride the bull.
我来这儿是为了骑公牛
Whoo!
哦!
We got another one to ride the bull!
我们又有一位来骑公牛的！
Okay, little doggie,
来吧，小美人
you're up.
你骑上来吧
Oh, fun.
哦，不行
I'm a doggie.
我只是说说
Oh. Whoo.
哦，呜！
Oh, yeah. I'm here to ride the bull.
好吧，我来骑公牛
Check it out. Whoo!
看好了，呜！
Yeah! Whoo!
Yeah!呜！
Baby!
Whoo!
呜!
Aah! Ooh.
啊! 呜.
Andrew, you promised you'd stay with your mother.
Andrew, 你答应过我和你妈妈住一起
That's why I gave you the car.
所以我才给你车的
Dad, she wants me out. She put all my stuff on the front lawn.
爸爸，她赶我走 她把我所有的东西都扔到草坪上
This is ridiculous.
太荒谬了
I'm going to call her, and I'm going to smooth all this out.
我会给她打电话 摆平这件事的
You're going home.
你回家吧
No, dad, why?
不，爸爸，为什么？
Now I can live with you without feeling guilty.
现在我可以毫无内疚 的和你住一起了
It'll be perfect. It'll be like our own little bachelor pad.
会很棒的 就像两个光棍住一起那样
What?
什么？
Son, that's not going to happen.
儿子，这不可能
Why not?
为什么？
Andrew...
you know, these --these last few months have been incredibly difficult for me.
这几个月对我来说已经非常困难了
There are a lot of things that I've got to work out for myself,
我得自己做很多事情
and I can't do it if you're living with me.
如果你和我住 我就无法应付了
I'm sorry.
对不起
I don't care, all right?
我不在乎，好吗？
I'm not going back there.
我不会回那儿的
I don't think you have a choice.
我认为你没有选择
But, dad --
但是，爸爸
unh-unh.
嗯哼
Oh.
哦
Come on now. Don't --
别这样
Heath?
Yeah, it's me.
是的，是我
Do you still have your fake I.D.?
你还有你的假身份证吗？
Yeah, I've got to go home and kiss my mother's ass, and I am not going to do it sober.
是的，我回家后挨了我妈妈冷屁股 我想喝醉了会感觉好点
"That was more than I needed to know."
我知道这些就够了
He was in shock. He was totally shocked.
他非常震惊
He says, "Congressman, this was a campaign.
他说：“议员们，这是一场运动
This was not the vote. You voted already."
这不是选举，但你们已经投票了”
That's what it was.
就是这样
I love that one.
我喜欢那个
Oh, the desserts look wonderful.
哦，甜点看起来棒极了
Lynette, do you need any help?
Lynette, 你需要帮忙吗?
I got it covered. No problem.
我可以的，没问题
Okay, Scavo, you're up.
好的, Scavo
Let's hear this genius idea of yours.
让我们听听你天才的想法
Okay.
好的
Uh...
呃
okay.
好吧
The single greatest obstacle facing Spotless Scrub is a lack of visibility.
无污擦面临的最大问题 是缺少知名度
We need to concentrate ad spending in places where women spend the majority of their time.
我们需要把广告投放在 妇女们经常出入的地方
For example, large chain grocery stores.
例如，大的连锁商店
Picture Spotless Scrub ads on the side of every mother's shopping cart.
无污擦广告的图片放在每个妈妈 的购物车里
Interesting.
有意思
Oh, you know what'd be even better?
哦，你们知道怎样会更好吗？
Dry cleaning bags.
干的清洁袋里
What?
什么？
No, really, hear me out.
听我说
Put a big Spotless Scrub ad between a woman and her cashmere sweater,
在一个女人和她的羊毛衫 中间放一个大的无污擦
I guarantee you'll get her attention.
我保证你们能引起她的注意
Honey, honey, that's great.
宝贝，宝贝，太棒了
I'm in the middle of a thing here.
我正说到一半呢
Oh.
哦
Look -- she's got a point.
对，她说到点子上了
I would notice that.
我应该注意这个
And those dry cleaning bags hang in our closets forever,
这些干净的袋子会永远挂在我们 的衣橱里
and so it is like constant advertising.
这像是在不断的做广告
Exactly.
正是
You know, maybe there's a way that we can work that in, but back to me.
你知道，我们也许可以那么做 但先听听我的
You know, Lynette, this is kind of a fantastic idea.
你知道吗, Lynette 这是一个绝妙的主意
Can we go nation wide with this?
我们能在全国范围这样做吗？
Why not? Start by targeting the top chain.
为什么不可以 从渠道的最顶端开始
Then branch out from there.
然后再分销下来
Boom, boom, boom
- mass saturation.
-集中渗透
Oh, you know what else would be a great idea?
哦，你们知道怎么做会更好吗？
Here's the thing...
这样的
While Lynette was commanding everyone's attention,
当Lynette 正在吸引每个人的注意时
Susan was trying to remain inconspicuous.
Susan 正努力的避人耳目
Everybody's looking at me, aren't they?
每个人都在看我，是吗？
Just the slapstick fans.
只是些低俗的爱看热闹的人
Oh, god, why couldn't I have just been knocked unconscious?
哦，上帝 刚刚为什么我没有被摔晕？
Beer?
要啤酒吗?
Absolutely.
当然要.
Oh.
哦.
Ow.
啊呜.
Ow, ow.
啊呜，啊呜
Susan, this is Kendra.
Susan, 这是Kendra.
We've been introduced.
你已经介绍过了
No, this is Kendra. We've been friends for years.
没有, 这是 Kendra 我们是多年的朋友了
She's here on a visit. She's leaving tomorrow.
她只是来看看我 明天就走
That's it.
就这样
It's true.
是真的
I have no designs on this man whatsoever.
无论如何 我对这个男人没什么企图
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
Sorry about the misunderstanding.
不好意思让你误会了
Me too.
我也是
So how long have you two been seeing each other?
你们在一起多久了
Well, you sort of interrupted our first date,
你破坏了我们的第一次约会
but up until then, smoking hot tension.
在这以前，只是互相观望
Sounds pathetic, I know.
听起来挺惨的，我知道
No, I think it's good to take it slow.
不，我觉得慢一点好
You'd be smart to be careful.
你这么做很聪明
Any particular reason?
有特别的原因吗？
Look, Mike's a wonderful guy, really,
Mike是个非常棒的男人，真的
but you should ask him why he moved to Wisteria Lane.
但你应该Wisteria Lane
It's one hell of a story.
这里大有缘由
Here, I got some ice.
我拿了些冰块过来
Here you go.
给你
Thanks.
谢谢
Well, it's been fun. Thanks, guys.
太有意思了 谢谢你们
See you later.
再见
Whoo-wee.
哦.
Good evening.
晚上好
Well, good evening.
Have a seat.
坐吧
I could get used to this whole closure thing.
我应该习惯这些关于分手的鬼话
I love long goodbyes.
我喜欢很长的分手
Wait around the corner. I'll be right back.
等在边上 我马上回来
Smile, Gabrielle.
笑一下，Gabrielle
Well, that's it, then.
已经这样了
What are you doing?
你干什么？
She had a camera. We've got to catch her.
她有相机，我们得抓住她
Mrs. Solis, your husband's going to kill us.
Solis夫人 你丈夫会杀了我们的
Come on!
喂!
Leave me alone!
别追我!
Give me that camera right now!
现在把相机给我！
Shut up.
闭嘴
I'm not kidding, old woman!
我不是开玩笑，老女人
Stay away from me! Don't touch me!
离我远点，别碰我
No.
不
No, you go home.
不，你回去吧
I'll take care of this.
我来处理
And you were never here.
记住，你从没来过这儿
Go.
走吧
Did you see that?
刚才你看见了吗？
That guy came barreling around the corner and just hit her.
那个开快车的家伙刚刚撞了她
Do you have a cell phone?
你有手机吗？
Yeah.
有
Call 911.
打911
As Juanita teetered dangerously close to the white light,
当Juanita 在生死边缘徘徊的时候
Lynette and Tom were headed into a black hole.
Lynette 和Tom 正吵得热火朝天
I was just participating.
我只是参与了一下
Well -- no, your participation was supposed to be limited to making dinner,
你的参与仅限于做晚饭
not making my ideas look bad.
而不是批判我的主意
Yeah, well, maybe you need better ideas.
哦，也许你需要更好的主意
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I didn't mean that.
对不起，对不起，我不是那个意思
No. No, no, no, no.
不，不
We both know that your career was going so much better than mine before we had kids.
我们都知道在有孩子之前 你的事业比我成功
You never let me forget that.
你永远也不让我忘记这一点
That is not fair.
这不公平
You're always competing with me,
你总是和我竞争
and judging by tonight, you know what? You still are.
就拿今天晚上来说，知道吗 你还在竞争
Tom, I am sorry about tonight, truly,
Tom, 今天晚上我真的很抱歉
but these days, if I'm competing with anyone, it's the Bree Van De Kamps of the world,
但这些日子，如果我和别人竞争的话 那只能是Bree Van De Kamps
with their spotless kitchens and their perfect kids who throw fabulous parties where nothing ever goes wrong.
她那完美的厨房，听话的孩子 举办宴会一切有条不紊
I try so hard to keep up, but I can't.
我很想赶上她，可是不行
Lynette, that's not my expecta--
Lynette, 这不是我所期望的
and when you work on a pitch or you bring the partners over,
当你帮你的同事带来时
I am reminded of a world I left behind where I was the winner
我又想起了那个被我抛在身后的世界
and people tried to keep up with me.
在那里我是赢家 人们总是努力赶上我
I can't go back. I can't win where I am.
我无法回去，我现在又赢不了
I am stuck in the middle, and it is really starting to get to me.
我被卡在中间了 真的让我太难受了
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. For your information,
咳,咳，咳，咳，咳 你这么说
I thought you threw an amazing dinner party tonight.
我觉得你今天准备的晚餐太惊人了
I was thrilled.
我太震惊了
I don't know how you pulled it all together.
我不知道你怎么把这些都扯倒一起
Yeah, well...
哦……
and whether you believe it or not,
不管你是否相信
everyone who knows you thinks that you are a great wife and mother.
每个认识你的人 都认为你是个优秀的妻子和母亲
No, they don't.
不，不是的
Yes, they do.
是的
Especially me.
特别是我
Thanks.
谢谢
What's wrong with your eyes?
你的眼睛怎么了？
Nothing. I'm tired.
没什么，我累了
Turn around. Wait a minute. I want to look at you. What --
转过来，等等 我想看看你
I'm fine, really.
我很好，真的
Wow, what's going on outside?
哇呜，外面怎么了？
Oh, my...
哦，天
oh, my god. Thank god you're here.
哦，天啊，感谢上帝，你在这儿
Will you go take care of Gabrielle? I have to go home for a minute.
你来照顾Gabrielle好吗 我回家一会儿?
All right.
好的
Oh, Andrew, thank god you're back.
哦, Andrew, 谢谢上帝你回来了
I need your help, honey.
我需要你的帮助，宝贝
There's been an accident.
发生车祸了
Andrew?
Mama?
妈妈?
Andrew.
Rex, you need to come home.
Rex, 你需要回一趟家
Something's happened, and we need you.
有事情发生了，我们需要你
Competition.
竞争
It means different things to different people,
因人而异
but whether it's a friendly rivalry
但是不管是友好竞争
or a fight to the death...
还是生死决斗
Cheers.
欢呼
The end result is the same.
结果总是相同的
There will be winners...
有赢家
and there will be losers.
也有输家
Of course, the trick is
但是，诀窍是
to know which battles to fight.
懂得去参加什么样的竞争
You see...
要知道
no victory comes without a price.
胜利都是用代价换来的